BELLO KIKELOMO ABIGAEL

Mobile: +234 7034948070 | Email: kiksbello@gmail.com 5 Bola Arowolo Street, Atunrase Estate, Gbagada Lagos.

SUMMARY

Experienced Account Manager and Business Development Manager with vast experience in managing clientele relationships and sales activities. Seasoned SAP account manager with expertise in business process management, people management, enterprise sales, vendor and partner relationship management. Possess technical know-how of managing projects, achieving increased revenue, recommending value added solutions while creating value for customers and stakeholders.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Oryx Computer Systems (W/A) – Account Manager, West Africa

February 2015 - Present

- Responsible for the management of clientele accounts through the entire sales process, implementation and ongoing support
- Build and maintain strong, long-lasting customer relationships
- Responsible for achieving assigned revenue targets/goals
- Responsible for recognizing additional opportunities within existing accounts with the aim of improving on revenue
- Develop a trusted advisor relationship with key accounts, customer stakeholders and executive sponsors
- Ensure the timely and successful delivery of solutions according to customer needs and objectives
- Communicate clearly the progress of monthly/quarterly initiatives to internal and external stakeholders
- Responsible for periodic forecasts and tracking of key account metrics
- Assist with high severity requests or issue escalations as needed
- Performance Management/experience
- Consistently surpassed all revenue targets whilst improving on customer satisfaction and channel efficiency
- Designed and implemented a workflow process to efficiently manage customer complaints, allowing for swift escalations within the channel through to the OEM

Oryx Computer Systems (W/A) – Support Consultant (SAP Solutions)

February 2014 - February 2015

- Effectively communicating and building consensus with clients
- Documenting current-state business processes and designing future-state processes
- Documenting implementation scope and design
- Defining and documenting requirements for software customizations and custom reports
- Manage customer complain messages and take the appropriate set to resolve their problems
- Managing customers' service requests, incidents and problems associated with SAP software through the use of SAP Solution Manager (SOLMAN)

Oryx Computer Systems (W/A) – Customer Executive

May 2013 - February 2014

- Meeting with client management to discuss and find out their new needs and requirement from our solution.
- Organizing and managing training session for super users and administrators
- Attending initial project meeting before project kick-off and creating project blueprints.
- Training of client's staff on the effective use of the SAP application.
- Manage customer complain messages and take the appropriate set to resolve their problems
- Handling Pre-sales meeting and Demos for new prospects and new sale opportunities.
- Offer support services to client and provide relevant solutions to enhance clients' productivity.

Semo & Co Nigeria Ltd. – Sales Representative Officer

March 2011 - September 2011

- Introduce and promote all current and new products to distributor network and end users
- Assist in training and motivation of new and existing sales personnel
- Maximize market penetration in assigned markets
- Evaluating competitive situations, coordinating of intelligence gathering and implementing appropriate tactics as required

United Bank for Africa Plc. - Customer Service Officer (NYSC)

April 2010 - February 2011

- Ensured effective and timely service delivery to customers
- Facilitate speedy problem resolution to customer complaints
- Received, evaluated and process all customer information requests
- Reviewed account opening documents and ensure timely opening of the accounts on the system for all requests with the required documents
- Processed customers cheque and card requests including ultimate delivery to the customer
- Accounts management and re-activation
- Ensured customer satisfaction through excellent customer service delivery and great interpersonal interactions.

EDUCATION

•	Master of Science, Organizational Behaviour – University of Lagos	2012
•	Bachelor of Science, Business Administration – University of Lagos	2009
•	Senior School Leaving Certificate – Mayflower Secondary School	2005
•	Primary School Leaving Certificate – O&A Nursery & Primary School	1999

PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATION

- Certification Project Management Institute
- Certification Advanced Microsoft Package (APTECH Worldwide)
- Certification SAP Presales & Sales Executive

COURSES AND TRAININGS

•	Price Waterhouse Coopers – Service Trainee "Take a girl student to work"	August 2009
•	SAP Business One Implementation Training	June 2015
•	SAP Challenger Sales Training	May 2016
•	SAP SMB Summer School	July 2019

SKILLS AND EXPERTISE

- Key Account Management
- Employee and Entrepreneur Business Experience
- Consulting, I.T & Manufacturing Experience
- New Business Development
- Strategic Support
- Marketing Strategy
- Customer Relations and Retention
- Service Delivery
- Forecasting and Identifying Key Opportunities

- Self-Motivated and Target Oriented
- Excellent Interpersonal Skills
- Leadership Skills
- Excellent Communication Skills
- Creative and Innovative
- Report Documentation
- Ability to Multitask
- Adaptability and Works under Pressure
- Resourceful